{
    "basicCard": [
        {
            "front": "King",
            "back": "Burger"
        },
        {
            "front": "Della",
            "back": "taco"
        },
        {
            "front": "Ronnie",
            "back": "McDonnie"
        },
        {
            "front": "Carlie",
            "back": "Junior"
        },
        {
            "front": "Kendra-Fry",
            "back": "Chicken"
        },
        {
            "front": "Queen",
            "back": "Dairy"
        },
        {
            "front": "Huttie",
            "back": "Piza"
        },
        {
            "front": "Freezie",
            "back": "Foster"
        },
        {
            "front": "First Fart",
            "back": "Smells"
        },
        {
            "front": "Where do we go now",
            "back": "downtown"
        },
        {
            "front": "In the heat and the rain",
            "back": "with whips and chains"
        },
        {
            "front": "Like a light in the black",
            "back": "I'm going home"
        },
        {
            "front": "The answer to life, universe and everything",
            "back": "42"
        },
        {
            "front": "Where are all of the tacos",
            "back": "On every corner"
        },
        {
            "front": "Between",
            "back": "H&H"
        },
        {
            "front": "The Q",
            "back": "The A"
        },
        {
            "front": "This Question",
            "back": "This Answer"
        },
        {
            "front": "Sammy",
            "back": "Hagar"
        },
        {
            "front": "Alice",
            "back": "Cooper"
        },
        {
            "front": "Input the Question",
            "back": "Input the Answer"
        },
        {
            "front": "What is 1 + 1",
            "back": "2"
        },
        {
            "front": "Here is the question",
            "back": "this is the answer"
        },
        {
            "front": "The Q",
            "back": "The A"
        }
    ]
}